[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All dogs are of the same species.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which city is a sister city to Eilat?", "correct_answer": "Los Angeles, California", "incorrect_answers": ["Hollywood, Florida", "West Palm Beach, Florida", "Boca Raton, Florida"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the movie Eight Below set?", "correct_answer": "1993", "incorrect_answers": ["1984", "1893", "2006"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The radius is a bone which is part of the human leg.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which 1997  movie was nominated for 14 Academy Awards?", "correct_answer": "Titanic", "incorrect_answers": ["Shakespeare in Love", "Gandhi", "The Last  Emperor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following cards has a converted mana cost of 2 in the game Magic: The Gathering?", "correct_answer": "Disenchant", "incorrect_answers": ["Ink-eyes, Servant of the Oni", "Shock", "Char"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Arecibo Observatory, located approximately 12 miles south-southwest from Arecibo, Puerto Rico, is notable for owning the worlds largest single-aperture telescope of this type.", "correct_answer": "Radio telescope", "incorrect_answers": ["Dioptric telescope", "Catadioptric telescope", "Catoptric telescope"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Dead Sea is part of the Great Rift Valley. How far does this valley extend in length?", "correct_answer": "3700 miles", "incorrect_answers": ["6700 miles", "697 miles", "1697 miles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On what game show did contestants receive unwanted joke prizes, called zonks?", "correct_answer": "Lets Make a Deal", "incorrect_answers": ["Family Feud", "Check-Out", "The Price is Right"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor, who stars as the teenage father in Juno, was also in at least 53 episodes of Arrested  Development as George-Michael Bluth.", "correct_answer": "Michael Cera", "incorrect_answers": ["Daniel Clark", "J.K. Simmons", "Daniel Wilson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tony Manero, the main character in the movie Saturday Night Fever, had posters of which actor?", "correct_answer": "Al Pacino", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert DeNiro", "Dustin Hoffman", "Harvey Keitel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Mel Brooks Silent Movie, Non is the only spoken word. Who has the only speaking part in Silent Movie?", "correct_answer": "Marcel Marceau", "incorrect_answers": ["Marty Feldman", "Mel Brooks", "Sid Caesar"]}]